{
    "id": "c88064a7223d4615a15921e98704b82e",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Identify the verb form from the given alternatives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smart",
                "speak",
                "sensitive",
                "division"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blanks with a suitable word. One gets …………………… in rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dry",
                "cold",
                "fresh",
                "wet"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Select the singular word from the following.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bacteria",
                "radii",
                "goose",
                "fungi"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Read the following sentence and find out the noun form from the given alternatives.  My car broke down on the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "car",
                "broke",
                "down",
                "my"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Complete the following sentence.  He ………………….. very fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drive",
                "drives"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Identify the adjective from the following sentence.  Susie writes beautiful poems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Susie",
                "writes",
                "beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Complete the following sentence.  I want to come with …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "she",
                "they",
                "you"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Complete the following sentence.  My dad …………………coming from Delhi tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Identify the punctuation mark () in the sentence.  Some men are born great some achieve greatness others have greatness thrust upon them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "colon",
                "semicolon",
                "hyphen",
                "inverted comma"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Identify the plural form from the options given below.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lice",
                "louse",
                "lices"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}